<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-25T22:40:52-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">TaniaPaiva</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><author><name>Tania Paiva</name></author><entry><title type="html">How I end up “reading” more</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/books/reading/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How I end up &quot;reading&quot; more" /><published>2020-02-24T15:28:54-03:00</published><updated>2020-02-24T15:28:54-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/books/reading</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/books/reading/">&lt;p&gt;One of my goals for 2019 was to read more, my idea was to read at least one book per month. I failed at this goal, and honestly I failed fantastically, because I started to read 5 books, and I couldn’t finished a single one. My reading list of articles increased daily but I was not able to make it go down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reasons because I failed in this goal are distractions and tiredness. By the end of a work day, my brain was really tired to dedicate another hour for reading, and during the day when having some free time I ended up spending those minutes in social networks. Yeah, as I said I failed fantastically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this post is not about my huge failure, instead is about how I end up improving my amount of reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So at the last days of December I was talking with a friend about the New Year goals, and I mentioned my failure on the reading goal, and I was like “you know what will be really cool?, if the app for saving lecture links could also read you with a cool voice, not too much robotic, so while you are like cleaning the dishes you could hear the articles you save” and he told me: 
“You already use pocket and it has that functionality”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there was the answer to fix my lecture issue. An app that I was already using but I never noticed about that functionality and then I lighting strike again, I have a kindle touch from 2012, with guess what? speakers and jack port.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, in just a week, I have listened to 8 articles of my pocket list and I have listened to 2 chapters of one of my books in the kindle, all this happened while I was washing the dishes and cleaning my apartment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I end up using all the tools I already have but in a little different way.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Tania Paiva</name></author><category term="reading" /><category term="pocket" /><category term="kindle" /><summary type="html">One of my goals for 2019 was to read more, my idea was to read at least one book per month. I failed at this goal, and honestly I failed fantastically, because I started to read 5 books, and I couldn’t finished a single one. My reading list of articles increased daily but I was not able to make it go down.</summary></entry></feed>